# Konstantin Kirgintsev WEB/UI-designer



Date of birth: 22 mar 1986 (30 years) Location: Russia, Saint-Petersburg

Relocation: Other countries

Phone number: +7 989 818 76 17 E-mail: <u>kirgintcev@gmail.com</u> Skype: kirgintcevatgmail.com

Instagram: kirgincev

# Objective:

Getting the Web/UI designer position in a strong team

#### Education:

Yalta University of Management (2003-2008) «Computer and automatic systems software»

## Summary of Qualifications:

Experience in website design and ui design - more than 7 years

Expert in most commonly used computer design applications (Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator) - 10 years. Axure, Scetch- 1 year. junior CSS3/HTML5/JS coding - 2 years. Adobe Muse, Adobe After Effect, Google Web Designer - 1 years

# Portfolio:

# http://portfolio.kirgincev.info/

# Experience:

Web/UI designer

Jun 2015 -

Freelance (topzakazz.ru olymptrade.com and other clients)

Web design, UI design, website redesign, landing pages, banner design, coding CSS / HTML, .ico design, animation

Web/UI designer

Nov 2014 - Jun 2015 (8 months)

CYAN (<a href="http://cyan-jobs.info/">http://cyan-jobs.info/</a>) Software development «Macshiny» and other Web design, UI design, website redesign, landing pages, banner design, coding CSS / HTML, .ico design, animation

Web/UI designer

Jan 2014 - Sep 2014 (9 months)

installmonster (http://installmonster.ru) Internet-marketing PPC

Web design, UI design, website redesign, landing pages, banner design, coding CSS / HTML

Web/UI/print designer Feb 2013 - Jan 2014 (1 year) Freelance

Clients: <u>rosa-tv.com</u>, <u>bibliotech.com.ua</u>, <u>motoshkola.com.ua</u>, <u>3k.com.ua</u>, <u>lh.com.ua</u>, gazetamfc.ru, caramel-koktebel.com

Web design, ui design, print design, graphics design, flash animation, coding CSS / HTML

Print/Web designer

Oct 2011 - Mar 2013 (1 year 6 months)

Love & Hunger (http://lh.com.ua) Catering

Print design, web banners design, graphics design

Web/print designer

Sep 2009 - Oct 2011 (2 years 2 month)

Freelance

Clients: <u>dibelena.com/eng/, ladjane.com, yaltavodokanal.com.ua, lesnoy-crimea.com</u>

Web designer

Feb 2009 - Sep 2009 (8 months)

New welle (http://welle.com.ua) Design studio

Web banners design, graphics design, web design, ui design, flash animation

Graphic/Print/Web designer

Sep 2008 - Feb 2009 (6 months)

ORT media (http://www.ortmedia.com.ua/) Advertising and PR Services

Print design, web banners design, graphics design

Reference List:

http://installmonster.ru/

Dmitry. Project Manager. Skype: dot.dm

http://lh.com.ua/

Julia. Chief Financial Officer. tel.: +38 067 758 19 67

Language skills:

English — intermediate. Russian — native. Ukrainian — native

Courses:

Web-design courses (2001 y)

MBTI:

ENFJ (2014 y)

Operating systems:

Windows, Mac OS

Other programs:

Microsoft Office, Open Office, Filezilla, Total Commander, NetBeans, Cinema 4D, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe After Effects, Microsoft Visual Studio